Guide to the Duke Student Government Records, 1960-2019 UA.31.02.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke Student Government records
1960-2019
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Student Government
UA.31.02.0002
28 Linear Feet
0.44 Gigabytes
The Duke Student Government (DSG) replaced the existing student government, Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), in 1993. DSG is the governing body of Duke undergraduate students and acts as the principal liaison between them and the University administration. It presents students' views on the affairs of the University community, appoints students to University and Board of Trustees committees, and oversees and allocates funds to student clubs and organizations. The Duke Student Government Records, 1960-2007, contain materials of both the DSG its organizational predecessor, Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU). Records consist of correspondence, legislation, minutes, reports, printed matter, judicial decisions, charters, memoranda, speeches, receipts, vouchers, and other materials, and document student governance and political activity, organizations, events planning, housing, and interaction with Duke University administration and the Board of Trustees.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
Provenance
The Duke Student Government Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer from 2001-2008.
Historical Note
The Duke Student Government (DSG) replaced the existing student government, Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), in 1993 under a new organization in which the legislative and executive branches were consolidated. DSG is the governing body of the undergraduate students at Duke University and acts as the principal liaison between the undergraduate student body and the administration. It presents the students' views on the affairs of the University community, passes resolutions on the students' behalf, and appoints students to all appropriate University and Board of Trustees committees. It also oversees, charters, and allocates funds to student clubs and organizations.
Collection Overview
The Duke Student Government Records, 1960-2019, contain materials of both the Duke Student Government (DSG, formed in 1993), and its organizational predecessor, the Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU, formed in 1967). Records consist of correspondence, legislation, minutes, reports, printed matter, judicial decisions, charters, memoranda, speeches, receipts, vouchers, and other materials. The collection documents a broad spectrum of student social life, including student governance and political activity, organizations, events planning, housing, and interaction with Duke University administrative officers, offices, and the Board of Trustees.
Arranged in order by accession number, except that in all cases Board of Trustees materials have been transferred to the Board of Trustees Series, housed at the end of the collection.
Related Material
Associated Students of Duke University Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Men's Student Government Association Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Woman's Student Government Association Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection contains electronic records that must be requested through the catalog and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Student participation in administration; Duke University -- Students -- Political activity; Duke University -- Student housing; Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- Students -- Social life and customs; Duke University. Board of Trustees; Associated Students of Duke University; Duke University. Student Government
- Accession UA 2001-37, 1994-2001, 1 box
  Scope and Contents note
  Records of the DSG's Vice-President for Academic Affairs, mainly from 2000-2001. Materials and topics include technology on campus, the tuition equalization policy on study abroad, dining services (ARAMARK), the Perkins Library renovation, legislative meetings, a history of DSG activities from 1999-2000, and the DSG Task Force on Financial Aid Report, 2000. Arranged as received.
  - Vice-President for Academic Affairs Records, 1994-2001, 21 folders (Box 1)
- Accession UA 2001-51, 1960, 1974-1998, 3 boxes
  Materials primarily cover the mid-1990s except for photocopies of a few earlier reports on curriculum review and long-range planning at Duke. Arranged as received, in two sequences that are roughly alphabetical by organization or topic.
  - Curriculum 2000 (C2K), Fall 1998, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Curriculum--older reports, 1974-1984, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - VOICE Sheets, Fall 1998, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Preceptorials, history of, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Minors, Fall 1994 (Box 1)
  - History of the Dean's Excuse Policy, 1988-1998 (Box 1)
  - History of Tuition Equalization Policy, 1998 (Box 1)
  - AALL major, undated (Box 1)
  - Academic Affairs Committee Notes, 1994 (Box 1)
  - ACES--preliminaries to, 1990 (Box 1)
  - ASDU Academic Interaction Project, 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Academic Standards Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Administration Flow Charts, 1994 Jan. (Box 1)
  - Admissions, undergraduate, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Achievement Index, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Asian Studies, Spring 1990 (Box 1)
  - Black Faculty Initiative, 1991-1994 (Box 1)
  - Career Center, 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - Center for International Studies, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Center for Teaching and Learning, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Curriculum Committee (Arts and Sciences), 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Curriculum Review Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Dance Program, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Diversity in the Curriculum, 1994, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - East Campus Enhancement Committee, Spring 1994 (Box 2)
  - Environmental Science Program, circa 1991 (Box 2)
  - Honor Code and Honor Council, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Independent Study reports, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Intellectual Climate Report, 1994 Apr. (Box 2)
  - Mid-semester grades and course evaluations, undated (Box 2)
  - The Perk, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Perkins Library Renovations, 1991 (Box 2)
  - DSG Project Renewal, circa 1993 (Box 2)
  - University Writing Course, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Legislative Matters, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Leadership Edge (John Hawkins), Fall 1996 (Box 2)
  - LIP Projects, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Meeting space, l996 (Box 2)
  - Newspaper articles, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - NPHC Party Policies, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - OSD Dean Search, 1996 July 11 (Box 2)
  - Party Policy, Triangle, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - President Keohane, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Senior Year Experience, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - PACOR, 1996-1997, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Panhellenic Association space proposal, 1996 Mar. (Box 2)
  - Phone lists, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Joe Pietrantoni, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Safe Rides/Walks, Summer 1996 (Box 2)
  - SACS, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - SOFC, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Sexual Assault Support Services (SASS) statistics, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
  - Stanford, U.S. News, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Student Education Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Safety Task Force, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Severe Weather Policy, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Student Advantage Card, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
  - Tenure Process, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Trustee Priority document, 1997 Jan. (Box 2)
  - Teaching Evaluation Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Trinity Board of Visitors, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - University Scheduling Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - US PIRG, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Dean White Retirement Dinner, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Yours Truly and Milestones, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Voter registration, 1996 (Box 2)
  - University Committee on Long Range Planning, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Leadership guidelines, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Student advising, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - American University, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Academic Policy Proposal, 1996 Oct. (Box 2)
  - Board of Trustees report (to DSG), 1996 Sept. 27 (Box 2)
  - Bryan Center Renovations, 1996 June-1997 Feb. (Box 2)
  - Cabinet, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - College Club System, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Student Conferences, Spring 1997 (Box 2)
  - Clubs/Organizations (University Life), 1997 (Box 2)
  - Current House Rules, undated (Box 2)
  - Dining Services, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Disciplinary report, 1995-1997 (Box 2)
  - DSG General Body Meeting, 1996 Sept. 18 (Box 2)
  - DSG Standing Committee Goals, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - DSG budget, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - DSG finances, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - EAC/One Stop Shop, 1994-1997 (Box 2)
  - Internship, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Letters for committee appointments, 1993-1997 (Box 2)
  - Bob Etheridge, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Executive notes and minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - 15-501 Citizen's Advisory Committee (CAC), 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Joel Fleishman, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Food Points Policy, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Grade Inflation Proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Jared Green, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Governor Jim Hunt, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Independent study, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Kudzu Cafe, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Late Breaking News program, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
- Accession UA 2003-0041, 1966-2003, 10 boxes
  The largest accession yet received, comprising about half the collection. Hundreds of topics are covered in these files, with the predominant category of materials being the agendas and minutes of various sessions of the ASDU and the DSG, from the early 1980s through the early 2000s.
  Arranged as received. Although there is no overall order to the accession, several runs of ASDU and DSG minutes appear in groups of twenty to eighty folders, and these help anchor various portions and periods of the materials.
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU) Legislature, 1987-1988 Session--weekly meeting agendas and minutes, 1987 Sept. 1-1988 Apr. 11, 24 folders (Box 3)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1988-1989 Session--weekly meeting agendas and minutes, 1988 Sept. 12-1989 Apr. 17, 24 folders (Box 3)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1989-1990 Session--weekly meeting agendas and minutes, 1989 Sept. 11-1990 Apr. 16, 24 folders (Box 3)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1991-1992 Session--weekly meeting agendas and minutes, 1991 Sept. 17-1992 Apr. 28, 24 folders (Box 3)
  - Student Organizations Commission (SOC) line items, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - SOC line items, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - SOC line items and funds, 1988-1989, 16 folders (Box 3)
    Contains budgets for the following funds and organizations: Club Fund, Black Student Alliance, The Chronicle, discretionary and executive funds, FAC, insurance, programming, Publications Board, SALAP, SARC, SCC, student fees, the Union, and WXDU.
  - Greek Life Task Force, 1993-1994, 6 folders (Box 3)
    Includes the task force's agendas, minutes, reports on Greek life at other institutions, draft and final reports, and newspaper articles.
  - Residential Life Task Force Report, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Duke Students and the Law: Campus Packet, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Race Relations, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Visions of Duke, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Summer Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Summer Advisory Committee, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Residential Plan Update, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Statute of DSG, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
  - DSG Legislature, 1995 Dec. 6 (Box 3)
  - SOFC advisors, 1998-1999 (Box 4)
  - SOFC agendas, 1999. Jan. 31-Feb. 21, 5 folders (Box 4)
  - SOFC bylaws, 1998 Sept. 13 (Box 4)
  - SOFC Chair Memo, 1998 Oct. 25 (Box 4)
  - SOFC budgets, 1999-2000 (Box 4)
  - Budget, NAACP-Psych Major, 1998-1999 (Box 4)
  - Budget, Best Buddies-Habitat, 1999-2000 (Box 4)
  - Budget, Future is Now-SMART, 1999-2000 (Box 4)
  - Budget, Steppin Up-Coffeehouse, 1999-2000 (Box 4)
  - Events on Points, undated (Box 4)
  - Faculty Associates, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Feminist Majorities, 1996 (Box 4)
  - 1st Year Orientation, 1995 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Harassment Policy, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Intro to Break for Change, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Keohane Luncheons, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Keohane Meetings, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Joe Pietrantoni, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Quad Development Committee, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Residential Facilities Task Force, 1995 (Box 4)
  - SACFAM, 1995 (Box 4)
  - SALAP, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Schedule Committee, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Academic Council, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
  - Alcohol Policy, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Association Board, 1996-1996 (Box 4)
  - Bryan Center Writing Project, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Down Under, 1989-1994 (Box 4)
  - East Campus Enhancement Task Force Report, 1994 (Box 4)
  - East Campus Freshmen Plan, 1993 (Box 4)
  - University Life, 1995 (Box 4)
  - WDDDM ideas, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Beijing Funding, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Black Faculty Initiative, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Building Bridges, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Christie Rule, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Citizens Advisory Group on 15/501, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Community Interaction, 1996 (Box 4)
  - College Student Survey, undated (Box 4)
  - Crowell Building space, 1995 (Box 4)
  - DSG Computing, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Duke Long Range Planning, 1995 (Box 4)
  - East Union, 1996 (Box 4)
  - President's Council on Black Affairs, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Residential Life on East Campus, undated (Box 4)
  - Sign-up Sheets: Fraternity/Sorority Life, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Sororities/Fraternities, undated (Box 4)
  - Traditions/Yours Truly, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Uncle Harry's Project, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Afro-American Chairs, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Community Relations Committee, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Dining Services, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Facilities and Athletics, 1999-2000 (Box 4)
  - Inauguration, 1995 (Box 4)
  - PCOBA, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - Residential Life Survey and Policy, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Legislative Act of 1995 (Box 4)
  - Legislator Packets, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
  - Legislature Election Results, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Programming Fund Request, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
  - DSG Legislature, 1996-1997 Session, Agendas and Minutes, 1996-1997, 5 folders (Box 4)
  - Executive Elections Budget Packet, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Legislature Campaign Policies, 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - Legislative Election Packet, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Bylaws, 2000 (Box 5)
  - DSG Legislature Meeting, 2000 Apr. 5 (Box 5)
  - The Legislative Act of 2000 (Box 5)
  - DSG Legislature, 2000-2001 Session, Agendas and Minutes, 2000 Oct. 4-2001 Apr. 18, 5 folders (Box 5)
  - University Committee Appointments (Academic Affairs, Community Interaction, Facilities and Athletics, and Student Affairs), 2001-2002, 4 folders (Box 5)
  - Budgets, 1995-1996, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Passed Legislation, 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - General Body Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 2001-2002, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Academic Affairs Minutes and Agendas, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Cabinet Meetings and Agendas, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Community Interaction Minutes and Agendas, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - DUSDAC Minutes and Agenda, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Facilities and Athletics Minutes and Agendas, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Residential Life Minutes and Agenda, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Student Affairs Minutes and Agendas, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - SOFC Minutes and Agenda, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Constitution of DSG, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Student Groups Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
  - SOFC Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - ASDU Representative Directory, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - Executive Meeting Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - External Affairs Committee Agenda, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - LegiCon Orientation, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - DSG Legislature, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - SOFC Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 5)
  - DSG Statutes, Bylaws, and Resolutions, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Election Bylaw, 2000 (Box 5)
  - SOFC Budget, 2002-2003, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Student Organizations Commission (SOC), 1990-1993, 18 folders
    - Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - General Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - ASDU Change, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Club Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Programming, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Depreciation, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Orientation, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Bylaws, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Information, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Audit, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Chair: Orientation, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Chair: Misc., 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Chair: Legi-Con, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Chair: Legislative Agendas, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Chair: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Chair: Legislation, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - Chair: Nominees/Committees, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
    - SOC Packets, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - ASDU Legislative Representative List, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1990-1991 Session--weekly meeting minutes, 1990 Sept. 17-Dec. 3, 10 folders (Box 5)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1990-1991 Session--weekly meeting minutes, 1991 Jan. 14-Apr. 15, 12 folders (Box 6)
  - ASDU Resolution Concerning the Advertisement by "The Committee for Open Debate on the Holocaust," 1991 (Box 6)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1992-1993 Session--weekly meeting minutes, 1992 Sept. 16-1993 Apr. 28, 5 folders (Box 6)
  - SOFC Club Budgets (Cultural), 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - SOFC Budget Hearings, 1996 Jan.-Feb., 4 folders (Box 6)
  - SOFC DUCS Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - SOFC Budget Proposal--New Asian Strings, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - SOFC Proposed University Union Budgets, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - SOFC Club Budgets A and B, 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - DSG Fund, Fiscal Periods 97/01 (July) through 97/07 (Jan.), 1996 Aug.-1997 Feb., 7 folders (Box 6)
  - Minutes, 1996 Sept. 18 (Box 6)
  - Report of DSG's Summer Activities, 1997 Sept. 7 (Box 6)
  - DSG Legislature, 1997-1998 Session, Agendas and Minutes, 1997 Sept. 14-1998 Apr. 28, 19 folders (Box 6)
    Minutes appear in most but not all folders
  - Agenda, 1998 Aug. 31 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 6)
  - DSG Retreat, 1997-1998 (Box 6)
  - Alumni Association, 1996-1997 (Box 6)
  - DSG Budget, 1995-1996, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - ASDU Legislature Agendas, 1983 Sept. 12-1984 Apr. 16, 25 folders (Box 6)
  - ASDU Legislature Agendas, 1984 Sept. 3-1985 Mar. 25, 21 folders (Box 7)
  - "Selection of a Student as a Trustee," memo from President Terry Sanford memo to ASDU Officers, 1977 Nov. 17 (Box 7)
  - ASDU Constitutions, 1969, 1974, 1977, 1981 (Box 7)
  - ASDU Constitution (Men's Student Government), 1967 (Box 7)
  - Unity Day, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Minority Affairs Review, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Safety/Residential Life/General Stuff, 1989 (Box 7)
  - UG Residential Philosophy and Policy of Duke, 1979 (Box 7)
  - President's Council on Black Affairs, 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Newsletters-BSA, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Diversity Council, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Residential Life Implementation, 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Residential Life Committee Report, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Parking, 1989 (Box 7)
  - SOFC Agendas, 1995-1996, 8 folders (Box 7)
  - SOFC Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - SOFC Club Programming Requests, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - SOFC Club Recognition Requests, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - SOFC Legislation, 1995 Sept. 13-1996 Feb. 19, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - SOFC Programming Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - SOFC Budget 1993 Oct. 27-1994 Jan. 27, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - SOC By-laws, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - SOC Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - SOC Audits, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - ASDU Legislation, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Student Organization Commission Budgets, 1992-1994 (Box 7)
  - DSG Legislature, 1993-1994 Session, Agendas and Minutes, 1993 Sept. 15-1994 Apr. 20, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - DSG Legislature, 1994-1995 Session, Agendas and Minutes, 1994 Sept. 14-1995 Apr. 19, 13 folders (Box 7)
  - DSG Legislature House Rules, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - DSG Student Groups, 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - DSG Budgets, 1993-1997, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - DSG Resolutions, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - ASDU Resolutions, 1990-1993, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - SOC Fiscal, 1987-1989, 9 folders (Box 8)
    Fiscal years 1987/88 and 1988/89 are mixed together in this folder group. Folder topics include: Bylaws, Policy Statements, Budgets, Programming Fund, General Requests, and Club Budgets.
  - SOC Fiscal, 1989-1990, 21 folders (Box 8)
    Folder topics include: Extra Papers; Club Fund, Depreciation Schedules, Student Fee, Union, Chronicle, Legislative Discretionary Funds, Club Fund, ASDU Insurance, Programming Fund, Executive, SALAP, BSA, FAC, SARC, CCC, CHANCE, Sports Club, WXDU, PUB Board, and General Requests.
  - SOC Fiscal, 1990-1991, 14 folders (Box 8)
    Folder topics include: Line-Item Budget, BSA, CCC, CHANCE, Depreciation Account, FAC, Student Fee, ASDU Insurance, Pub. Board, SALAP, Sports Club Council, WXDU, General Requests, and Club Fund.
  - ASDU Legislature, 1984-1985 Session--Agendas and Minutes, 1985 Apr. 1-1985 Apr. 15, 4 folders (Box 8)
    [Processor's note: there are two copies of Apr. 1 minutes--one folder of approved minutes and one of April Fool's minutes (unlabeled as such).]
  - ASDU Legislature, 1985-1986 Session--Agendas and Minutes, 1985 Sept. 9-1986 Apr. 14, 25 folders (Box 8)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1985-1986 Session--House Rules and Protocol (Box 8)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1985-1986 Session--By-Laws (Box 8)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1985-1986 Session--SOC Info (Box 8)
  - ASDU Legislature, 1986-1987 Session--Agendas and Minutes, 1986 Nov. 17-1987 Apr. 13-20, 18 folders (Box 8)
  - Residential Life (Undergraduate), 1994, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Residential Planning, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Student Affairs, 1996-1997 (Box 8)
  - Busing Advisory Board, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Diversity Committee, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Housing Policy, 1996-1997 (Box 8)
  - DSG Constitution, 1993 (Box 8)
  - East Campus Enhancement Committee, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Organizations correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - ASDU editorials on Willowhaven Country Club, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Housing Study Commission's Report to ASDU, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Report of the Subcommittee on Organization of Residential Colleges, 1984 (Box 8)
  - ASDU Committee Interviews / Administrative Sec. Responsibilities, 1986, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Budget for Undergraduate Publications / Study Abroad Committee Minutes, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Housing Policy Committee, 1996 (Box 8)
  - DSG Constitution, 1995 (Box 8)
  - "History of ASDU, 1967-1977," by Christopher Hest, 1978 (Box 8)
  - University Committee on Facilities and Environment, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - Council on Black Affairs, 1994-1996 (Box 8)
  - Academic Council, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - Admissions, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - Administrative correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - Alcohol Policy, 1994-1996 (Box 8)
  - Duke Annual Fund--Parents Program, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Affairs Winter Board Meeting, 1995 Mar. 3-5 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Distinguished Alumni Award, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Arts and Sciences Council, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Reforming ASDU, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Constitutional review, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Georgia Tech Student Government, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Athletic Affairs, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Auxiliaries Services-general, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees agenda mailing schedule, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Student-Trustee interaction, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Dates, 1994 (Box 9)
  - ASDU/DSG By-Laws, 1992-1995 (Box 9)
  - Charity Benefits, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Check cashing, 1994-1995 (Box 9)